She seeks the power to free her people.
In the Lost Lands is a action, fantasy, western
film directed by Paul W. S. Anderson.
A queen sends the powerful and feared sorceress Gray Alys to the ghostly wilderness of the Lost Lands in search of a
magical power, where she and her guide, the drifter Boyce, must outwit and outfight both man and demon.
Gray Alys, played by Milla Jovovich.
Boyce, played by Dave Bautista.
The Enforcer, played by Arly Jover.
The Queen, played by Amara Okereke.
The Patriarch, played by Fraser James.
Jerais, played by Simon Lööf.
In the Lost Lands is a 2025 action fantasy film directed by Paul W.
Anderson, with a screenplay by Constantin Werner from a story they co-wrote.
Based on the short story of the same name by George R.
Martin, the film stars Milla Jovovich and Dave Bautista as a witch and a hunter,
respectively, who journey into a dangerous landscape to find an artifact for a queen.
In the Lost Lands was first released in Australia on February 27, 2025, and was released in the United States on
March 7, 2025, by Vertical in North American territories, and by Constantin Film Verleih in Germany.
The film explores themes of witch, dystopia,
sorcery, betrayal, based on short story.